millatfacebook.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy » Love . Peace . Joy

 **Our Privacy Policy  
**  
**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our footer menu. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the millatfacebook(MyMfb.com) website. The types of personal information collected is: 

Name   
D.O.B                                                                                                                                                                                                      
Phone number   
Email Address

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when signing up to let you register for millatfacebook(MyMfb.com). We do not share this information with outside parties.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MFB. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.   
**  
How  You Can Access Or Correct Your Information **

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by going to your account settings and privacy settings. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.

*Updated January 25th, 2012 (1st Rabiul Awal 1433 Hijri)

_Page has been viewed 382 times.._
